Guide to the Arthur Lee Loeb papers M1590
Dept. of Special Collections & University Archives
- Series 1: Correspondence
  - Correspondence: SIGMA XI Scientific Research Society (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: SIMPSON, Stephen M., Jr. (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: SINGMASTER, David (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: SKINNER, B.F. (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: SMITH, Prof. Cyril Stanley (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence: SMULLIN, Louis (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence: SNELSON, Kenneth (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence: South Shore Art (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence: SPAEPEN, Frans (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence: SPALDING, Andrew (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence: STEVENS, Peter S. (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence: STORTZ, Robert (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence: STROCK, Dr. Lester W. (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence: STRUIK, Dr. H. J. (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence: STUART, Prof. Duncan R., North Carolina State University (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence: STUBBS, Frederick W. (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence: SWIRNOFF, Lois (1 of 4) (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence: SWIRNOFF, Lois, photocopy of ts "Dimensional Color" (2 of 4) (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: SWIRNOFF, Lois, (3 of 4) (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: SWIRNOFF, Lois, (4 of 4) (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: SZABO, Prof. Albert Harvard (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: TECHNION - Israel Institute of Technology (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: TISHLER, Elizabeth (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: TUFTS University (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: University of North Carolina (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence: VAN ARKEL, Prof. Anton E. (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence: VARNEY, William (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Curtis, William (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Fehn, Ann Clark (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Gill, Susan (1 of 2) (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Gill, Susan (2 of 2) (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Gray, Jack (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Griffth, David M. (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Horn, Prof. Roger Duane (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Jellinek, Prof. Dr. F (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Joel, Dr. Nahum (IBELL-UNESCO) (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Johnson, Scott & Jim (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Kappraff, Prof. Jay (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - Katz, Prof. Lewis (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - Keffer, Prof. Fredric (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - Kellogg, David (Box 60, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence: Coxeter, Prof. H.M.S. (photocopies) (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: Franksen, Prof. O.I. (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: Kennard, Dr. Olga (with Bernal, Dr. John D.) (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: Kepes, Prof. Gyorgy (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: Kiest, Curt & Debbie (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: Kim, Scott (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: Kirsh, Andrea (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: Komoski, Dr. P. Kenneth (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence: Koptsik, Prof. Vladimir A. (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence: Land, Richard I. (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence: Lalvani, Prof. Haresh (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence: Lamson, Prof. Roy (M.I.T) (Box 67, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence: Laves, Prof. Dr. Fritz H. (Box 67, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence: Leger, Jeanne (Jeanne Leger Hughes-Evans) (Box 67, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence: Libowitz, Prof. George G. (Box 67, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence: Lima de Faria, Jose (1 of 2) (Box 67, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence: Lima de Faria, Jose (2 of 2) (Box 67, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence: Malkus, Steven (Box 67, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence: Mitchell, James (Harvard Alumni Dinner Series) (Box 67, Folder 19)
  - Nieuwenhuyse-MacGillavry, Prof. Dr. C.H. (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - Perry, Prof. William G. (Bureau of Study Counsel) (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - Reggini, Prof. Horacio C. (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - Thompson, Ben (Lincoln Laboratory) (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - Universite de Liege (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence 1 (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence 2 (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence 3 (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - A. Loeb personal miscellaneous (Box 81, Folder 9)
  - Arthur Loeb general & miscellaneous correspondence 1956-58 (Box 81, Folder 10)
  - Arthur Loeb general & miscellaneous correspondence 1959-63 (1 of 2) (Box 81, Folder 11)
  - Arthur Loeb general & miscellaneous correspondence 1959-63 (2 of 2) (Box 81, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence re: Synergetics (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - Synergetics dictionary - from Ed Applewhite (photocopy) (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence re: Buckminster Fuller (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: miscellaneous re: Bucky Fuller & related projects (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: Ed Applewhite (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - Ed Applewhite draft intro to Synergetics dictionary (Box 89, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: Coxeter, H.S.M. (Donald) (Box 89, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: preface to Synergetics (Box 89, Folder 8)
- Series 2: Publications
  Series 2, Publications, consists primarily of articles and books by Arthur Loeb, but includes some by Buckminster Fuller and others.
  - Crossing & Re-crossing the Angstrom Gap (ICA article & drafts) (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Peter Klein article (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - NASA speech by Buckminster Fuller (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - A Studio for Spatial Order by A. Loeb (+ ms draft) (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Synergy, Sigmoids & the &th year Infurcation by A. Loeb (photocopy of ms) (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Papers & presentations by various arthors (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - MIT Press: Geometrical and Chromatic Symmetry in the Plane by A. Loeb (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - MIT Press: The Electrical Double Layer Around a Spherical Colloid Particle by A. Loeb (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Appleton-Century-Crofts (general) (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Appleton-Century-Crofts Program Material (1of 3) (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Appleton-Century-Crofts Program Material (2of 3) (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Appleton-Century-Crofts Program Material (3 of 3) (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - W.A. Benjamin Publishing Inc. (Addison Wesley Publishing) (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Synergetics: MacMillan Publishing Preview Packet (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Birkhauser Boston, Inc. Publishers (1 of 5) (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Birkhauser Boston, Inc. Publishers (2 of 5) (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Birkhauser Boston, Inc. Publishers (3 of 5) (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Birkhauser Boston, Inc. Publishers (4 of 5) (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Birkhauser Boston, Inc. Publishers (5 of 5) (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Birkhauser Boston, Inc. Publishers brochures for "A Fuller Explanation" (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Technische Hogeschool Twente (1 of 3) (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Technische Hogeschool Twente (2 of 3) (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Technische Hogeschool Twente (3 of 3) (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - ACTA I: A Binary Algebra Describing Cyrstal Structures with Closely Packed Anions (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - ACTA II: A Binary Algebra Describing Cyrstal Structures with Closely Packed Anions (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - ACTA III: A Modular Algebra for the Description of Cyrstal Structures (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - ACTA IV: Subdivision of the Hexagonel Net and the Systematic Generation of Crystal Structures (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Automatische Rekenmachines: Whirlwind I (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Conductance and Relaxation Time of Electrons... (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Digital Computer as Laboratory Tool (SIAM) (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Evaluation & Analysis of Optical & Electrical Constants of Thin Films (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - "Go to the Devil!" essay by A. Loeb (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Dimensional Color Structure by Uri Feldman Ph.D. candidate (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Intro to Wave Mechanics by Loeb & Harris (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Space Structures by A. Loeb (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Space Structures: revised bibliography and artwork (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Space Structures: printer's proof + photocopy of TS (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Schaefer's Structures by Ernest Schaefer (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - R. Buckminster Fuller by John McHale (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Scientific American July 1965 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Physics Today June 1985 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Influence of Covalence on Ion Ordering and Distortion in Spinels (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Modulera Crystal Modules: A Teaching and Research Aid in Solid State Physics (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Reflection & Transmission of Radiation by Metal Films... (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Remarks on Some Elemenatry Volume Relations between Familiar Solids (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Symmetry Relations in Design (abstract) (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Symmetry: The Case History of a Program (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Theory of Ionic Ordering... (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous Publications by A. Loeb (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - 'Logical Machines" draft, Typescript + photocopies (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Early draft of "Logical Machines", chapters II & III, typescript and copies (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - "On the Harmony as Regularity" by M.A. Marutayev (TS) (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Shaping Space: A Polyhedral Approach ed.Senechal/Fleck photocopy w/ annotations (1 of 2) (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Shaping Space: A Polyhedral Approach ed.Senechal/Fleck photocopy w/ annotations (2 of 2) (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - "Space-filling Polyhedra" by A. Loeb (MS) (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - A Systematic Survey of Cubic Crystal Structures (draft) (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - A Systematic Survey of Cubic Crystal Structures (request for reprints) (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Interionic Attraction Theory Applied to Diffuse Layer Around Colloid Particles. I (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Calculation of the Electrophoretic Mobility of a Spherical Colloid Particle (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Theory of the Envelope Type of Thermal Conductivity Tests (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Thermal Conductivity. II, VIII. Measurement of Thermal Conductivity of Refractory Materials (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Ansiotropy in Antiferromagnetic Crystals with Rock Salt Structure (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Index - A.L. Loeb publications (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Papers: miscellaneous (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Russian Chemical Bulletins (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - "Vector Equilibrium in Crystals" (MS) (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous publications \ Trimtab (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Operating Manual for Spaceship Earth (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Synergetics 3rd draft photocopy (1 of 11) (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Synergetics 3rd draft photocopy (2 of 11) (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Synergetics 3rd draft photocopy (3 of 11) (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Synergetics 3rd draft photocopy (4 of 11) (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Synergetics 3rd draft photocopy (5 of 11) (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Synergetics 3rd draft photocopy (6 of 11) (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Synergetics 3rd draft photocopy (7 of 11) (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Synergetics 3rd draft photocopy (8 of 11) (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Synergetics 3rd draft photocopy (9 of 11) (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Synergetics 3rd draft photocopy (10 of 11) (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Synergetics 3rd draft photocopy (11 of 11) (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - Synergetics miscellaneous material (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Space Structures by A. Loeb, draft + mss (1 of 3) (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Space Structures by A. Loeb, draft + mss (2 of 3) (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Space Structures by A. Loeb, draft + mss (3 of 3) (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Concepts & Images by A. Loeb, markup draft mss (1 of 3) (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Concepts & Images by A. Loeb, markup draft mss (2 of 3) (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Concepts & Images by A. Loeb, markup draft mss (3 of 3) (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Various Loeb publications (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous publications (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Various Harvard Publications (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Morphological Aspects of Space Structures by LALVANI, Haresh (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous publications by LALVANI, Haresh (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Theory of Symmetry and Ornament by JABLAN, Slavik V. (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Newspaper clippings (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Binary Algebra Describing Crystal Structures by A. Loeb (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Structure and Patterns in Science and Art by A. Loeb (Leonardo reprint) (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous publications by A. Loeb (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - "A Renaissance Man in a Competitive Culture?" by A. Loeb (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Symmetry: the Case History of a Program by Loeb & Haughton (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Magic of the Pentangle: Dynamic Symmetry from Merlin to Penrose by Loeb (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Symmetry in the Plane - Teacher Material (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Symmetry in the Plane: A Program of Self Instruction (1 of 5) (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - Symmetry in the Plane: A Program of Self Instruction (2 of 5) (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - Symmetry in the Plane: A Program of Self Instruction (3 of 5) (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - Symmetry in the Plane: A Program of Self Instruction (4 of 5) (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - Symmetry in the Plane: A Program of Self Instruction (5 of 5) (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - Kennecott Refining: Ingot Casting & Stacking (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Ledgemont Laboratories: TR-74 A Program of Automatic Instruction, Symmetry in the Plane + draft (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Ledgemont Laboratories: memos, FLETCHER, E. W. (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Ledgemont Laboratories: publications featuring Loeb crystals (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Ledgemont Laboratories: Structure, Systematology and Communication by A. Loeb (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Ledgemont Laboratories: Symmetrical Subdivision of the Euclidean Plane by A. Loeb & LeCorbeiller (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Ledgemont Laboratories: Communication in a Technological Environment by Loeb & Servi (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Ledgemont Laboratories: memos and miscellaneous publications (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Ledgemont Laboratories: On Growth Functions by A. Loeb (Technical Note 49) (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Ledgemont Laboratories: Connectivity Relations in Space by A. Loeb (Technical Report 12) (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Ledgemont Laboratories: A Crystal Algebra for Laves Phases by A. Loeb (Technical Report 15) (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - International Journal of Space Structures V.6, no.4 1991 (Half-box 88, Folder 1)
  - A Comparative Study of the Development of Architecture & Music ca. 1720-1940 by A. Loeb (Half-box 88, Folder 2)
  - VES 165 History of Modern Architecture (A Comparative Study of the Development of Architecture & Music ca. 1720-1940) (Half-box 88, Folder 3)
  - On the Interaction of Colloidal Particles by S. Levine (Half-box 88, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous reprints, clippings (Half-box 88, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous publications, reprints, brochures (Half-box 88, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous publications: American Institute of Chemists directories (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous publications: Cambridge Center for Behavioral Studies 1988 & 1989 (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous publications: Chariton Review - Loeb articles (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous publications: Directory of Physics & Astronomy staff 1986-1987 (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous publications:Harvard Media (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous publications:International Cultural Exchange (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous publications (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous publications: ISIS Order/Disorder Book Abstracts (Box 91, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous publications: Fundamental Problems of Creating in Two Dimensional Space by Naomi Asakura (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - Leonardo: drafts, correspondence, miscellaneous (1 of 4) (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - Leonardo: drafts, correspondence, miscellaneous (2 of 4) (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - Leonardo: drafts, correspondence, miscellaneous (3 of 4) (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - Leonardo: drafts, correspondence, miscellaneous (4 of 4) (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - Dimensional Color: full color unbound copy (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - Dimensional Color: additional unbound pages (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - Arthur Loeb's publications/reprints/presentations, 1950s-1990s (Box 106, Folders 109, Box 105, Folders 1-10)
- Series 3: Faculty/Coursework
  Series 3, Faculty/Coursework, primarily relates to the Harvard University Visual and Environmental Studies Department. It includes correspondence, committees, curriculum review, exhibisitions, Task Forces and reports, lectures, etc.
  - Harvard/VES Dept. General files (1 of 4) (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Harvard/VES Dept. General files (2 of 4) (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Harvard/VES Dept. General files (3 of 4) (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Harvard/VES Dept. General files (4 of 4) (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Harvard/VES Dept. Visiting Committee 1970 (1 of 2) (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Harvard/VES Dept. Visiting Committee 1970 (2 of 2) (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - VES Dept. Teaching collection (1 of 3) (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - VES Dept. Teaching collection (2 of 3) (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - VES Dept. Teaching collection (3 of 3) (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Harvard: VES 138 (1 of 4) (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Harvard: VES 138 (2 of 4) (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Harvard: VES 138 (3 of 4) (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Harvard: VES 138 (4 of 4) (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Course materials, MIT course 6.25 (1 of 2) (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Course materials, MIT course 6.25 (2 of 2) (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - VES Dept. Misc. files (1 of 3) (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - VES Dept. Misc. files (2 of 3) (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - VES Dept. Misc. files (3 of 3) (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - VES Dept. Carpenter Center misc. (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Visual & Enviromental Studies correspondence (1 of 3) (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Visual & Enviromental Studies correspondence (2 of 3) (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Visual & Enviromental Studies correspondence (3 of 3) (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - CUE course guide evaluations (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Innovation course misc. (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Design Science 3 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Design Science 25, original draft (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Design Science 25, make ready copy (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Design Science 25, registration forms (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Design Science 25, planning & correspondence (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Design Science 25, misc. (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Design Science class, Anne Smith Duncan (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence re: job search and establishment of Loeb coursework & lab at Harvard. (1 OS binder) (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Harvard: V.E.S. Tenth Anniversary (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Harvard: V.E.S. Curriculum Review (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Harvard: V.E.S. Advising (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Harvard: Freshman Seminar Program (1 of 5) (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Harvard: Freshman Seminar Program (2 of 5) (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Harvard: Freshman Seminar Program (3 of 5) (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Harvard: Freshman Seminar Program (4 of 5) (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Harvard: Freshman Seminar Program (5 of 5) (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Lecture Outlines & Course preparation (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - A.L. LOEB - Lectures, Exhibits, etc. (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Burgundy: Rise & Gall of the Middle Realm notes & teaching materials (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Burgundy course: additional materials/House Seminars (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Harvard University: Office of the Arts (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Harvard University: Capenter Center Exhibition 1966 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Harvard University: Capenter Center Exhibition 1972 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Tutorial & Thesis Task Force/Studio Curriculum Task Force (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Harvard University: Faculty Research Study Group (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Harvard University: University Extension Courses (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Harvard University: Summer School 1972 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Harvard University: Special Concentration 1980's (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Harvard University: Special Concentration 1990's (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Harvard University: Task Forces & Reports (1 of 2) (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Harvard University: Task Forces & Reports (2 of 2) (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Harvard University: Task Forces & Reports (2 of 2) (Box 40)
  - Design Science: photocopy of markup draft (1 of 2) (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Design Science: photocopy of markup draft (2 of 2) (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - MIT Summer Program Correspondence & class materials 1961 &1962 (1 of 2) (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - MIT Summer Program Correspondence & class materials 1961 &1962 (2 of 2) (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Student Environment Committee Dratft Report (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: 17-Plane Symmetry Groups Course (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Harvard: General & Miscellaneous (1 of 3) (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Harvard: General & Miscellaneous (2 of 3) (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Harvard: General & Miscellaneous (3 of 3) (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Harvard: Graduate School of Design (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Harvard: Graduate School of Education (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Harvard: Hasty Pudding (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Faculty/Coursework: Head Tutors (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Harvard: Hoopes Prize Committee (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Harvard: International Host Family Program (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Harvard: Japan Project (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Harvard: Lecture Series Committee (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Harvard: Memorial Church (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Harvard: Philomorphs (1 of 5) (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Harvard: Philomorphs (2 of 5) (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Harvard: Philomorphs (3 of 5) (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Harvard: Philomorphs (4 of 5) (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Harvard: Philomorphs (5 of 5) (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Harvard: Project Physics (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Harvard: Project Physics (film) (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Harvard: Programmed Teaching (1 of 3) (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Harvard: Programmed Teaching (2 of 3) (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Harvard: Programmed Teaching (3 of 3) (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Harvard Shop Club/ The Signet Society (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Erasmus material (1 of 3) (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Erasmus material (2 of 3) (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Erasmus material (3 of 3) (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Erasmus Lectureship miscellaneous (1 of 2) (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Erasmus Lectureship miscellaneous (2 of 2) (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Erasmus Lectureship Committee (1 of 3) (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Erasmus Lectureship Committee (2 of 3) (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Erasmus Lectureship Committee (3 of 3) (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Erasmus Lectures (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Erasmus Lectures 1982- (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Erasmus Lectureship Committee 1974-75 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Erasmus Lectureship Committee 1976-77 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Erasmus Meeting November 7, 1986 (1 of 3) (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Erasmus Meeting November 7, 1986 (2 of 3) (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Erasmus Meeting November 7, 1986 (3 of 3) (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - NUFFIC: Netherlands Universities Foundation for International Cooperation (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous Dutch language material (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - VES 175 Spring 1973 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - VES 175 Fall 1973 with CUE 3D (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - VES 176 Fall 1993 includes class notes & assignments (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - EXT School Misc. (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - VES 176 S'94 with CUE (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - VES 175 Fall 1994 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - S 94-95 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - VES 176 Spring '95 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - S 1993 Questionnaires (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Contacts (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - CUE 1996/1997 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Philadelphia exhib. S1994 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - CUE 1997-98 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - VES 176 Spring 2002 (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Harvard/VES Department stuff (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - Topic Logos (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - Spring 2000 (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - VES 175 Fall 2000 (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - VES 176 Jan. 30 - Apr. 25, 1985 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - VES 176 homework file Fall '90 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Loeb VES 176 Fall 1991 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - VES 176 Visual Mathematics class list (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Coop Book Orders (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Handout on "e" (Chapter 3, Irrational number) photocopies (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Harvard Mechanics Memos (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Visiting Committee (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Grading Statistics (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - CUE Guide Statistics (Box 54, Folder 10)